<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/</link><description>Recent content in Home on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 08:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>California Wonder</title><link>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/california-wonder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/california-wonder/</guid><description>Blocky and wide, with crisp, thick walls and sweet taste. Ideal for stuffing, slicing into rings for dips and salad toppings, and chopping into crisp bite-sized nibbles. Delicious raw, stuffed and baked, stir-fried or grilled.
Type Bell Heritage Heirloom Color Dark green Size 4in x 4in Days to Harvest 75</description></item><item><title>Camelot</title><link>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/camelot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/camelot/</guid><description>Specially bred to produce large fruits with a classy shape. Plants produce heavy, firm, 3 to 4-lobed, glossy green fruits with thick, firm walls.
Type Italian Bullhorn Heritage Hybrid Color Green Size 4.5in Days to Harvest 74</description></item><item><title>Candy Cane</title><link>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/candy-cane/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/candy-cane/</guid><description>These unique sweet beauties will stand out in gardens. Elongated fruits ripen from green with creamy white stripes to solid red. Thin walls and crispy texture make it perfect for fresh eating at any stage of ripeness. Plants have unusual variegated foliage giving them an ornamental look.
Type Bell Heritage Hybrid Color Green Size 3-4in x 1-2in Days to Harvest 60-65</description></item><item><title>Emerald Giant</title><link>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/emerald-giant/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/emerald-giant/</guid><description>The thick-walled, dark-green to red peppers have a sweet, juicy taste and crisp texture. Has more vitamin C than an orange. Excellent for salads, stuffing, or baking. Vigorous plants give heavy yields. A good variety for the south.
Type Bell Heritage Open pollinated Color Green Size 4-5in Days to Harvest 75</description></item><item><title>Golden California Wonder</title><link>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/golden-california-wonder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/golden-california-wonder/</guid><description>Golden-yellow at full maturity, these peppers are thick-walled, meaty and really sweet and tasty. Square shaped fruits grow upright on healthy plants, making harvesting easy.
Type Bell Heritage Heirloom Color Green to yellow Size 4in Days to Harvest 73</description></item><item><title>Red Bull</title><link>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/red-bull/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/red-bull/</guid><description>Extra-large, blocky bell pepper is very thickwalled and capable of becoming just huge. Peppers begin as dark green and ripen to a candy apple red, the stage when the fruit is very sweet and most nutritious.
Type Bell Heritage Hybrid Color Green to red Size 5in x 5in Days to Harvest 75</description></item><item><title>Sprinter</title><link>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/sprinter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/sprinter/</guid><description>Very early bell. High yields of beautifully formed, big, blocky peppers with excellent flavor. Healthy plants are robust growers and perform well regardless of temperature.
Type Bell Heritage Hybrid Color Green to red Size 3.5in Days to Harvest 60</description></item><item><title>Tolli's Sweet Italian</title><link>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/tollis-sweet-italian/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vmagro.github.io/plant-markers/plants/tollis-sweet-italian/</guid><description>Perhaps the best overall heirloom pepper. Italian heirloom consistently produces big yields of bright red fruits that are equally good for frying, canning, eaten fresh or added to tomato sauce.
Type Cubanell Heritage Heirloom Color Red Size 5in Days to Harvest 75-85</description></item></channel></rss>